forexmegacashback.com 2016-10-15

# Forex Mega Cash Back - Legal Information

## Legal Information

Trading Forex on margin carries a high level of risk, and may not be suitable for all investors. The high degree of leverage can work against you as well as for you. Before deciding to invest in foreign exchange you should carefully consider your investment objectives, level of experience, and risk appetite. The possibility exists that you could sustain a loss of some or all of your initial investment and therefore you should not invest money that you cannot afford to lose. You should be aware of all the risks associated with foreign exchange trading, and seek advice from an independent financial advisor if you have any doubts.

Forex Mega Cash Back - FMCB respects the privacy of the individual and appreciates the confidence of its customers, partners, and employees. This Privacy Policy identifies the practices of FMCB for the collection, use and dissemination of information that yourself may provide us on FMCB website. Please read the entire Privacy Policy before using this website or provide any information to FMCB. 

By using this website 'FMCB' you agree that you understand, accept and agree to these Terms of Use and Forex Mega Cash Back Privacy Statement.

## Information collection, uses and share

FMCB does not collect the information that identifies persons such as your name, address, phone number or email address. That only happens when a member 'user' provides this information voluntarily to FMCB Admins. FMCB may use this information to contacting users to provide more information or to improve this website, or may be used to provide users with information requested or any additional information may interest you such as offers or services. This information will always be kept private between users and FMCB thus it will not be circulated outside FMCB scope without users' prior consent. FMCB may use this information to conduct studies on the market or for other commercial purposes.

FMCB respects customer privacy, and will not interchange or debate or disclose any of the customer information directly or indirectly or information in relationship with FMCB, but with the same user, including customer account information, capital and all of the terms of trading, and maintained by FMCB in a very narrow range within FMCB to serve the users satisfactorily, and FMCB maintains the right to prevent the client 'users' from the publication of this information and within the scope of FMCB in the application of the Privacy Policy law.

FMCB may collect and store information locally on users’ devices using mechanisms such as browser web storage and application data caches. FMCB uses several advanced technologies to collect and store information when users visit FMCB website, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to users’ devices. 

FMCB may maintain the data that have been collected in a database includes personal information that has been given voluntarily by users.

FMCB records the total number of visitors to its Website, and the number of visitors to each of its pages in addition to the domain name of the resource visitor's Internet service, but we do not collect any personally identifiable information in the context of this process.

FMCB does not share Information with any 3rd-party company(s) such as unrelated brokers, organizations, or individuals, or statical companies, or even outsiders for whatsoever reasons.

Traders have to know thoroughly the high risk at this kind of investment which is considered the highest risk business due to various number of reasons to gaining and losing while trading Forex. Because of that, it is very possible to loss some or all your capital funds in this market as well as gaining partial or double amount of your capital thus Forex Mega Cash Back - FMCB administrations advise all traders to trade unnecessary funds for their lives. Trading Forex doesn’t necessarily depend on certain fundamental or technical analysis and neither on economic news (major or minor news) to gain or loss. It is very possible that economic news is positive and the price direction is negative and vice versa when economic news is negative the price goes positive. It is also possible that when economic news is positive the price goes positive, and when economic news is negative the price goes negative. There are other factors that may cause high risk in trading Forex such as high leverage while trading, low liquidity on a group of currency pairs or a certain pair, consuming high margin (used margin), and high liquidity entering the opposite direction of the trader’s trades and so on.

Traders have to know that prices may go one direction up or down for long term based on the market conditions and circumstances, and the impact of global economy. As a result of such factors, a high risk exposure to traders personal accounts lead to what is known as “margin call” where trader’s orders might all closed automatically. Thus Forex Mega Cash Back - FMCB advise all traders to learn as much as possible about the forex market before entering with real fund “money”. Traders as well advised to use tight stop-loss as a key prevention to protecting their equity.

All that being exposed to real personal account of losses is the result of the performance of the account holder as it is personal responsibility except in the cases where crashes or a technical glitch in brokers platform server happen or failure of its connection to trading platform itself or inability to run the platform, connect the user interruption command or a sudden explosion of market price “price spike” on the stage of the company without the same to happen in the real market or any technical issue may happen similar to that.

Also, although the account information should be confidential to the same account holder as it may not be granted which was to maintain the security of the account from being exposed to piracy or theft.

Here, FMCB admins stress once again that trading foreign currencies or shares or stocks using margin carries a high risk and may not fit all investors. Therefore, Forex Mega Cash Back - FMCB advise all novices and professional investors to be aware of the dangers of this type of investment before starting. Also, we advise everyone to carefully consider investment objectives and personal learning and training enough with / using virtual money “demo account” to practice enough before entering the market with real money.

All written articles, threads and posts by either of moderators, visitors and/or members don't necessarily express FMCB admins' opinions, but it is an individual opinions, and FMCB is not responsible for all that. All articles and threads on FMCB club is for the purpose of education only, and aimed to be used for clarification or explanation for all readers. And thus posts and threads made by members are based on individual analysis and opinions. Also, that evaluation of Forex brokers, articles and threads made by members "traders" don't express FMCB admins' opinion, but it is based on group or personal experience. Note that the historical data and information provided or display anywhere at FMCB website is not an indicator of what is going to happen in the future. And based on that, traders "members" at FMCB must understand the high risk level may cause as a result of using these data and infomation.

And once again, Forex Mega Cash Back - FMCB is not responsible about any failure or damage caused to clients’ accounts as a result of account holder activity(ies) or performance, and that each account holder is responsible for his/her account credentials of being kept private and never to be distributed by any mean or share it with anyone. Any failure or damage caused by a Forex broker platform is considered to be the Forex broker’s responsibility(s) and therefore the broker is liable to all accounts’ holders who their accounts got damaged or harmed by that kind of glitch or failure. Forex Mega Cash Back - FMCB warn all traders to read this notes patiently to be aware of the type of risk in this investment.

## Changes to these Terms and Policies

Forex Mega Cash Back - FMCB reserves the right to update or change these terms of use and the privacy policy at any time. Such changes will be posted without notice on this Web page.

Forex Mega Cash Back - FMCB management / Administration - **Last Updated on 2013-08-09**
